# Resha Puspita Dewi

Bandung, Indonesia | +62821 3032 0607 | reshapuspitadewi@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

Undergraduate Student in Information System and Technology major with internship experience as Web Developer. Enjoyed content creation as an instrument to support a learning process. Confident to gain new experiences in a sector that can empower people to improve their level of needs continuously.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Loker Programmer (Medan, Indonesia)

Front End Programmer Intern (August 2020 - October 2020)

- Develop interactive website using ReactJS in collaborated with cross-functional teams
- Integrate Front-End components with RESTful API to develop fully functioning web page

#### ProBotDev Sdn Bhd (Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia)

Scrum Master Apprenticeship (April 2019 - June 2019)

- Responsible to provide project boards for software engineer (SE) teams
- Enable scrum implementation in a team with 4 members
- Collaborate with product owner to deliver instruction to the team

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Institut Teknologi Bandung (2017-Present)

Bachelor of Engineering

#### **SKILLS**

- Basic programming
- Web development: Ruby, Javascript
- Mobile (Android) development: Java, Kotlin
- Database: MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- Development testing: Postman, Katalon Studios

## TRAINING/CERTIFICATIONS

- Electives Lite x Tokopedia Academy (June 2021)
  - Testing in Scale with Tokopedia Engineering Productivity Course
- Generasi GIGIH by Yayasan Anak Bangsa Bisa (YABB) (May 2021-August 2021)
   Backend Engineer
- Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka (February 2021-July 2021)

  Mobile (Android) Development Participant
- Impact Byte (June 2020-August 2020)
  - Full Stack Web Graduate

## **VOLUNTEER AND ORGANIZATIONS**

## HMIF ITB (March 2019-March 2021)

Academic and Welfare Staff

- Responsible to input study resources into shared drive throughout the semester
- Responsible to share information related to academics and scholarship with the members.

## IAIF ITB Scholarship (October 2019)

Head of Logistic BNI ITB Ultra Marathon Event

• Lead logistic team to prepare basecamp used by alumni in the event.

#### Lingkar Sastra ITB (November 2017-May 2020)

Head of Infrastructure & Household Division (2019-2020)

Member of Craftmanship Division (2018-2019)

- Have a discussion with the member to appreciate literary works
- Responsible to organize seminars and competitions related to literature.
- Responsible to accommodate the literary works of members to be published into physical work.

## **SOCIAL MEDIA**

**LinkedIn**: linkedin.com/in/reshapuspita/

**Github**: github.com/renvelvet

Medium: medium.com/@renmaar